{
    "subject": "resource/Hot_Coffee_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/distributor",
    "object": "resource/HBO",
    "human_readable": "The distributor of the film 'Hot Coffee' is HBO.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9031246900558472,
            "question": "Besides 'Hot Coffee', what other films has HBO distributed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8950855731964111,
            "question": "Is HBO a distributor of movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.868465781211853,
            "question": "Who distributed the film 'Hot Coffee'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8461077213287354,
            "question": "Which film was distributed by HBO?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7179977297782898,
            "question": "What is the name of the company that distributed 'Hot Coffee'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6147449612617493,
            "question": "What type of content does HBO typically produce and distribute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5963907241821289,
            "question": "Is 'Hot Coffee' a well-known film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5553606152534485,
            "question": "Can you name any other movies distributed by HBO?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3425590395927429,
            "question": "What kind of media company is HBO?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32830139994621277,
            "question": "Does HBO also produce original television series?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The distributor of the film 'Hot Coffee' is HBO.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6409_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of media company is HBO?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6409_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other movies distributed by HBO?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6409_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Hot Coffee' a well-known film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6409_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6409_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Hot Coffee\" was sold to HBO, which suggests that HBO is indeed the distributor of the film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that Susan Saladoff's documentary \u201cHot Coffee\u201d was sold to and distributed by HBO. Therefore, the statement that the distributor of the film 'Hot Coffee' is HBO is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}